When you start to learn about all of the things that go on behind the scenes with people in
power, it starts to make you feel like there is nothing that can be done to change the
direction of the world.
And then you see professors come out and form, you know, a human chain around their students
praying to Allah at NYU.
You see professors marching on the Columbia campus demanding that their students be unsuspended.
And you start to see that though it is different things that will wake people up to their humanity
and that will cause people to step out beyond the fear that has held them back, you at the
very least find joy in the fact that there is something that caused that.
There is something that made folks say enough is enough.
And when people wonder why people protest, why there is disruption, why folks like me
continue to keep speaking ad nauseum, it's because you never know what day that is going to hit
someone and make them say, it is time for me to stop being a bystander and time for me to
start being human.